[The Epoch of Miyu]
[미유시대]
[Episode 28]
[28회]
Over there.
저기요.
Be careful. Slow down.
조심하세요. 천천히 하세요.
Come on. Close your eyes.
어서 해봐요. 눈을 감으세요.
Done.
완료.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Take a look at today's schedule.
오늘의 일정을 살펴보세요.
It's all here.
모든 것이 여기에 있습니다.
Keep an eye on it.
계속 지켜봐주세요.
Got it.
알았어요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Mr. Xiao, you need to keep an eye out later.
샤오 씨, 해야 할 일 나중에 주의하세요.
When Zhichun talks about
Zhichun이
this year's college entrance exam,
에 관해 이야기할 때 올해 대학 입시,
I'll give you a signal.
신호를 보내드릴게요.
Then, you can go on stage.
그러면 무대에 오르시면 됩니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Miyu.
미유.
Your time to go on stage
무대에 올라갈 시간이야
might not be fixed.
고쳐지지 않을 수도 있습니다.
It mainly depends on Kuanli's sales.
주로 Kuanli의 매출에 달려 있습니다.
The host might cue you to go on stage at any time.
호스트가 당신에게 다음과 같이 신호를 줄 수도 있습니다. 언제든지 무대에 오르세요.
Let me know if there are any problems.
문제가 있으면 알려주세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Welcome to Purong Hotel.
푸롱 호텔에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
How is it?
어때요?
It's starting.
시작됩니다.
Hello, everyone.
여러분, 안녕하세요.
Hello to everyone.
여러분 안녕하세요.
Welcome to my live stream channel.
내 라이브 스트림 채널에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
I wonder if there are any
어떤 것이 있는지 궁금해
college entrance exam-takers watching my live stream right now.
대학 입학 시험 응시자 지금 내 라이브 스트리밍을 보고 있어.
There's only half a month left until the college entrance exam.
이제 보름밖에 남지 않았네요 대학 입시 전까지.
I don't know
모르겠어요
if every family with a college entrance exam-taker
모든 가족이 함께 있다면 대학 입시 응시자
is giving it their all for a final push.
마지막 추진을 위해 모든 것을 바치고 있습니다.
Considering that it's a critical moment
지금이 매우 중요한 순간이라는 점을 고려하면
for exam-takers,
시험 응시자를 위한
we want to provide
우리는
convenience in terms of your travel.
여행의 편리함.
In the following time, the product in our live stream
다음 시간에는 실시간 스트림에 나온 제품
will be special.
특별할 것이다.
We have achieved a strategic cooperation
우리는 전략적 협력을 달성했습니다
targeting the newly added exam site
새로 추가된 시험 사이트를 타겟팅
this year
올해
with nearby five-star hotels
근처 5성급 호텔과 함께
for accommodation and dining.
숙박과 식사를 위해.
We hope that we, who have been through it,
우리는 그런 일을 겪어본 사람,
can provide
제공할 수 있습니다
students who are about to take the exam
시험을 앞두고 있는 학생
with a high-end service during the exam period.
고급 서비스로 시험기간 동안.
The first one is Kuanli Hotel.
첫 번째는 관리호텔입니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Please have a seat.
자리에 앉으세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
The one who is sitting next to me is
내 옆에 앉아 있는 사람은
Mr. Xiao from the Marketing Department of Kuanli Hotel.
마케팅 부서의 Mr. Xiao 관리호텔.
Let me introduce
소개할게요
I guess everyone has heard of
모두가
[Is this price real]
에 대해 들어본 적이 있을 것 같아요. [이 가격이 실화인가요]
Kuanli.
관리.
[Well, staying at Kuanli costs too much]
[글쎄, 관리에 머무르는 데 비용이 너무 많이 든다]
It is the best domestic hotel brand
국내 최고의 호텔 브랜드입니다
as well as the leader of domestic high-end hotel chains.
뿐만 아니라 의 리더 국내 고급 호텔 체인.
This guy talked even more arrogantly than I do.
이 사람은 더 거만하게 말했네 나보다.
By the way,
그런데,
ask
물어보세요
who the representative of Purong is.
푸롱의 대표는 누구인가.
I heard that Lu Zhenzhen went to have a baby.
루 젠젠(Lu Zhenzhen)이라고 들었는데 아기를 가지러 갔다.
Who could Ji Feng find to replace her?
Ji Feng은 그녀를 대신할 사람을 찾을 수 있을까요?
Xu Miyu, the Front Office's lobby manager.
프론트 오피스 로비 매니저 Xu Miyu.
Since our live stream has just started,
실시간 스트림이 막 시작되었으므로
let's put up ten orders to warm up.
워밍업을 위해 10개의 명령을 내리자.
Three, two, one,
셋, 둘, 하나,
link in the chat!
채팅에 링크!
The area of Kuanli's standard double room
관리 스탠다드 더블룸 면적
is 35 square meters.
35제곱미터입니다.
What? All gone?
무엇? 모두 사라졌나요?
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
I haven't finished introducing the product yet.
아직 끝나지 않았어 아직 제품을 소개하지 않습니다.
It proves that everyone
모두가
knows Kuanli Hotel very well.
Kuanli 호텔을 아주 잘 알고 있습니다.
After all, it's a well-known hotel.
역시 유명한 호텔이군요.
Let's do ten more orders?
10개만 더 주문하자?
Okay.
좋아요.
Okay, let's put up ten more orders.
좋아, 10개만 더 주문하자.
[Kuanli is doing a promotion]
[관리가 프로모션 중이에요]
Link in the chat!
채팅에 링크를 걸어주세요!
[The supply is limited]
[수량이 한정되어 있습니다.]
Mr. Xiao.
샤오 씨.
Some followers just asked
일부 팔로워가 방금 질문했습니다
if there are any catering services included.
만약 있다면 모든 케이터링 서비스가 포함됩니다.
Well, we need to ask Mr. Xiao about this.
글쎄요, 이것에 대해 샤오 씨에게 물어봐야 해요.
You still have to go to our restaurant
아직 우리 식당에 가야 해
for regular consumption.
정기적인 섭취를 위해
Kuanli's discount
관리의 할인
is mainly on the accommodation.
주로 숙소에 있어요.
Sold out again?
또 매진됐나요?
[My child is taking the exam at Xinhua Finance and Economics School]
[우리 아이가 시험을 보고 있어요. 신화재경대학]
[This is the biggest discount ever, right]
[역대 최대 할인입니다. 오른쪽]
Everyone is really so enthusiastic.
다들 정말 열정적이에요.
Mr. Xiao,
샤오 씨,
do we still have rooms available?
아직 예약 가능한 방이 있나요?
The last five orders?
최근 주문 5개요?
Director Zhao, are you kidding me?
자오 감독님, 농담하시나요?
You promised to give me plenty of rooms.
나에게 방을 많이 주겠다고 약속했잖아요.
Mr. Duan Jr.,
두안 주니어 씨,
we only have 25 rooms left,
방이 25개밖에 남지 않았네요
and I gave them all to you.
그리고 나는 그것들을 모두 당신에게 주었어요.
Kuanli has 460 rooms in total.
관리에는 총 460개의 객실이 있습니다.
You only gave me 25 rooms?
나한테 방 25개만 줬어?
Are you kidding?
농담하는 건가요?
Thank you very much, Mr. Xiao,
샤오 씨, 정말 감사합니다
for coming to our live stream room.
실시간 스트림 룸에 와주셔서 감사합니다.
Cut the crap.
쓰레기를 자르십시오.
I need another hundred rooms.
방이 100개 더 필요해요.
Followers, don't be anxious.
추종자 여러분, 걱정하지 마십시오.
-Don't leave our live stream room. -Miyu.
-라이브 스트림 방을 떠나지 마십시오. -미유.
-If you didn't get rooms in Kuanli, -Get ready, please.
-관리에서 방을 구하지 못한 경우, - 준비해주세요.
it doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Because next,
왜냐하면 다음은
what we are going to introduce is
우리가 소개할 것은
the promotion targeting the college entrance exam
프로모션 타겟팅 대학 입학 시험
of Purong Hotel, which enjoys the same reputation as Kuanli.
푸롱 호텔의 Kuanli와 같은 평판.
Let's welcome
환영합니다
the lobby manager of Purong Hotel,
푸롱 호텔 로비 매니저
[I don't think I can get a room]
[방을 구할 수 없을 것 같아요]
[It's still expensive even though it gives discounts]
[아직도 비싸요 할인을 해주긴 하지만]
Xu Miyu.
쉬미유.
Do you trust me?
당신은 나를 신뢰합니까?
Last night at the Kuanli Hotel entrance,
어젯밤 관리호텔 입구에서,
I saw Francis,
프란시스를 봤어
the designated chef of
the designated chef of
the Global Internet and Venture Capital Summit.
의 지정된 요리사 글로벌 인터넷과 벤처캐피탈 서밋.
His appearance there is an indicator.
그의 외모에는 지표가 있습니다.
There's a high probability
가능성이 높습니다
the Summit will be held at Kuanli again this year.
정상회담이 다시 관리에서 개최됩니다 올해.
You know,
있잖아,
the number of attendees
참석자 수
is nearly 400 every year,
매년 거의 400명이에요,
which means at that time,
이는 그 당시에
Kuanli will definitely be fully booked.
Kuanli는 확실히 예약이 꽉 찼을 것입니다.
Are you sure?
확실합니까?
You can ask your friends about it.
친구에게 이에 대해 물어볼 수 있습니다.
It's not a secret project.
비밀 프로젝트가 아닙니다.
Moreover,
게다가
this year's summit
올해 정상회담
will be held earlier, in early June.
더 일찍, 6월 초에 개최됩니다.
It will coincide with the college entrance exam.
와 일치할 것이다 대학 입학 시험.
So, no matter whose products are promoted first,
그러니 상관없어요 누구의 제품이 먼저 홍보되는지,
Kuanli definitely won't make this money.
Kuanli는 확실히 이 돈을 벌지 못할 것입니다.
So, you were prepared in advance?
그럼 미리 준비하셨나요?
Hotel workers never go into battle unprepared.
호텔 직원들은 절대 전투에 참여하지 않습니다 준비되지 않은.
Welcome. Welcome.
환영. 환영.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Please have a seat.
자리에 앉으세요.
So next,
그럼 다음은
let's invite Ms. Xu
Ms. Xu를 초대하자
to introduce
소개할
the rooms in Purong Hotel for examinees.
푸롱호텔 수험생들을 위한 객실입니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Thank you, Ms. Dianjiangchun.
감사합니다, Dianjiangchun 씨.
[Huge discounts]
[대규모 할인]
Hello, everyone.
여러분, 안녕하세요.
I am Xu Miyu, the lobby manager of Purong Hotel.
저는 쉬미유입니다. 푸롱호텔 로비 매니저.
[My cousin needs it]
[사촌이 필요해요]
This time, Purong Hotel
이번에는 푸롱 호텔
will provide rooms on the upper floors,
위층에 객실을 제공할 예정입니다.
from the 12th to the 17th,
12일부터 17일까지,
exclusively for college entrance exam-takers
독점적으로 대학 입시 수험생
from June 6 to 10.
6월 6일부터 10일까지.
There are two reasons.
두 가지 이유가 있습니다.
First, the upper floors are quiet.
첫째, 위층은 조용합니다.
Second, we think
둘째, 우리는
concentrating these rooms
이 방들을 집중시키고 있어
can provide everyone with a
모든 사람에게
better review atmosphere.
리뷰 분위기가 더 좋아졌습니다.
Think about it.
생각해 보세요.
If your next-door neighbor
옆집 이웃이
and the neighbor next to them
그리고 그 옆에 있는 이웃
are all reviewing for the exam,
모두 시험을 검토하고 있어
wouldn't it feel like
그런 느낌이 들지 않을까
studying at school?
학교에서 공부해요?
Awsome!
굉장해!
Everyone,
여러분,
listen carefully.
잘 들어보세요.
Purong Hotel is offering
푸롱 호텔이 제공하는 서비스
entire floors of rooms for you.
당신을 위한 객실의 전체 층.
Let's imagine.
상상해 봅시다.
It's like living in a school dorm.
마치 학교 기숙사에 사는 것과 같습니다.
Everyone around is
주변의 모든 사람들은
exam-takers preparing for the exam.
시험을 준비하는 수험생들.
The atmosphere is awesome!
분위기가 굉장해요!
Yes.
예.
[Best rooms for college entrance exam candidates ever]
[최고의 객실 대학 입시 후보자 역대]
I noticed someone is asking
나는 알아차렸다 누군가가 묻고 있어
[Want to eat Yan Du Xian]
[Yan Du Xian을 먹고 싶다]
about the food.
음식에 대해서.
Let me explain it.
설명하겠습니다.
[I'll try to book Purong's room]
[푸롱이 방 예약을 해볼께요]
We will prepare set meals for you.
우리는 당신을 위해 정식을 준비할 것입니다.
[Purong has a bigger discount than a Kuanli]
[푸롱이 할인폭이 더 커요 관리보다]
The menu will be updated on our official website
메뉴가 업데이트됩니다 공식 웹사이트에서
in the near future.
가까운 미래에.
During the exam period, we will
시험 기간 동안 우리는
provide exam-takers with a wide variety of
시험 응시자에게 다양한
tasty and nutritious set meals.
맛있고 영양가 있는 정식.
The cost of the set meals
정식 비용
is included in the total price.
총 가격에 포함되어 있습니다.
This is also a way for Purong Hotel
이것은 푸롱 호텔을 위한 길이기도 합니다
to support and encourage the examinees.
수험생을 응원하고 격려합니다.
[Moms are eager to grab rooms]
[엄마들이 방 구하는데 열심이에요]
Someone is asking
누군가가 묻고 있어요
[Comparing to Kuanli, Purong provides a bigger discount]
[관리에 비해 푸롱은 더 큰 할인]
if the set meals include Yan Du Xian and boat pastries.
세트메뉴에 포함된 경우 Yan Du Xian과 보트 페이스트리.
Yes, they are included
예, 포함되어 있습니다
in our set meals.
우리 정식에.
At the same time,
동시에
we will serve breakfast half an hour earlier than usual
우리가 아침 식사를 제공할 거예요 평소보다 30분 일찍
to give the examinees plenty of time to eat.
수험생들에게 주려고 먹을 시간이 많음.
And after dinner,
그리고 저녁 식사 후에
we will add a supper,
저녁을 추가하겠습니다
so that students reviewing at night
학생들이 밤에 복습하도록
can also enjoy the meal service.
식사 서비스도 즐길 수 있어요.
We can also deliver meals
식사 배달도 가능해요
directly to the examinees' rooms.
수험생실로 바로 이동합니다.
The 100 orders are sold out.
100개 주문이 매진되었습니다.
[My Internet connection is poor. Can I make an offline reservation]
[인터넷 연결 상태가 좋지 않습니다. 오프라인 예약이 가능한가요]
Gosh.
이런.
[Sold out in such a short time]
[이렇게 짧은 시간에 품절]
We are going to set a record today.
오늘 우리는 기록을 세울 예정입니다.
Let's add 50 more orders.
주문을 50개 더 추가해 보겠습니다.
No problem.
괜찮아요.
Three, two, one.
셋, 둘, 하나.
Link in the chat!
채팅에 링크를 걸어주세요!
[It's time to put my reflexes to the test]
[이제 시간이 됐어. 내 반사 신경을 시험해 보세요]
[I'm ready]
[준비됐어요]
Ms. Xu, look, someone is asking,
Ms. Xu, 보세요, 누군가가 묻고 있어요,
"The discount is huge,
"할인이 엄청나네요,
[I will feel sorry for the room if my kid doesn't do well in the exam]
[방이 아쉬울 것 같아요 우리 아이가 시험을 잘 못 보면]
if I'm not an examinee,
내가 수험생이 아니면
[Non-exam-takers envy you a lot]
[비수험생들이 많이 부러워해요]
can I still book a room?"
아직도 방을 예약할 수 있나요?"
[Can I enjoy the discount as well]
[할인 혜택도 누릴 수 있나요]
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I have to disappoint this friend.
이 친구를 실망시켜야 합니다.
Purong Hotel
푸롱 호텔
is dedicated to creating the best learning environment for students
학생들을 위한 최고의 학습 환경
during the college entrance exam period.
대학 입시 기간 동안.
This is
이것은
our priority.
우리의 우선순위.
So, we won't violate our prioritized principle
그러니 우리는 위반하지 않을 것입니다 우리의 최우선 원칙
for our performance.
우리 공연을 위해.
At the same time, we will also strengthen
동시에
security measures during this period.
이 기간 동안의 보안 조치.
For example, upon check-in,
예를 들어 체크인 시
we will check and register
확인하고 등록하겠습니다
your admission ticket number.
귀하의 입장권 번호.
During the stay,
머무는 동안
we will arrange special security guards
특별 경비원을 배치하겠습니다
to irregularly patrol and inspect
비정기 순찰 및 검사
each floor
각 층
to ensure everyone's safety.
모두의 안전을 보장하기 위해.
Sold out.
매진되었습니다.
So fast!
정말 빠르다!
This tells us that
이것은 우리에게
in this seemingly saturated commodity market,
이 겉으로는 포화된 것 같아 상품 시장,
there are still many
아직 많아
unseen demands.
보이지 않는 요구.
First of all, we should also thank
우선, 우리도 감사해야 합니다
these two leading hotels
이 두 개의 주요 호텔
for noticing the needs of the examinees
수험생의 요구사항을 파악하기 위해
with such keen insight.
이렇게 예리한 통찰력으로.
Someone is asking that
누군가가 그걸 묻고 있어요
why you just provided a few rooms.
왜 방 몇 개만 제공했는지요.
Can you provide more rooms?
방을 더 제공해 주실 수 있나요?
Some also said their Internet is too slow
어떤 사람들은 그들의 인터넷이 너무 느리다
so they failed to book a room.
그래서 그들은 방을 예약하지 못했습니다.
[What a pity! I didn't get it]
[안타깝네요! 이해하지 못했어요]
There are still 20 minutes left.
아직 20분 남았습니다.
[Is there any spare room]
[여유 공간이 있나요?]
I'm sorry.
미안해요.
We still have
아직
20 minutes left,
20분 남았습니다.
but our stock is already gone.
그런데 우리 재고는 이미 없어졌어요.
We can provide more rooms.
우리는 더 많은 객실을 제공할 수 있습니다.
How many?
얼마나 많은가요?
A hundred orders.
백 주문.
Add another hundred orders!
또 다른 100개 주문을 추가하세요!
Three, two, one.
셋, 둘, 하나.
Link in the chat!
채팅에 링크를 걸어주세요!
Add another hundred orders!
또 다른 100개 주문을 추가하세요!
Three, two, one.
셋, 둘, 하나.
Link in the chat!
채팅에 링크를 걸어주세요!
Cut the crap.
쓰레기를 자르십시오.
I want another hundred rooms.
방 100개를 더 원해요.
It's impossible, Mr. Duan Jr.
불가능해요, Duan Jr.
Please don't make this hard for me.
제발 나를 힘들게 하지 마세요.
Parents and students
학부모와 학생
who haven't ordered yet,
아직 주문하지 않은 사람
-you need to seize the last chance. -Get lost!
-마지막 기회를 잡아야 한다. - 길을 잃다!
I also want to ask Ms. Xu.
저도 Xu 씨에게 물어보고 싶습니다.
Is Purong Hotel offering all of its rooms
푸롱 호텔은 모든 객실을 제공하고 있나요
for examinees?
수험생을 위해?
Here,
여기,
on behalf of Purong Hotel, I promise
푸롱 호텔을 대표하여 약속드립니다
that during the exam period, all our rooms will be reserved exclusively
즉 시험기간 동안 우리 방은 모두 독점적으로 예약될 거예요
for exam-takers.
수험생을 위한.
Even if there are empty rooms, they won't be used for other purposes.
빈 방이 있어도 다른 목적으로 사용되지 않습니다.
Excellent!
훌륭해요!
What are you looking for?
무엇을 찾고 있나요?
Where are the car key?
자동차 열쇠는 어디에 있나요?
Where is it?
어디입니까?
Here.
여기.
Thank you. Okay.
감사합니다. 알았어.
Where are you going?
어디로 가시나요?
To pick someone up.
누군가를 데리러.
That's wonderful. This is probably the first hotel in the country
정말 훌륭해요. 이것은 아마도 국내 최초의 호텔일 거예요
that exclusively serves families with college entrance exam candidates.
가족에게만 서비스를 제공하는 대학 입시 수험생들과 함께.
I'm touched by your sincerity.
당신의 진심에 감동받았습니다.
Since families with college entrance exam-takers
가족이 있기 때문에 대학 입시 수험생
count on us,
우리를 믿어요,
we won't let you down
우리는 당신을 실망시키지 않을 거예요
as Purong Hotel's principle is
푸롱 호텔의 원칙은
to serve our guests with sincerity
정성을 다해 손님을 모시겠습니다
and exchange sincerity for sincerity.
그리고 진심을 진심으로 바꾸세요.
Oh my.
아, 이런.
The students taking the exam at Xinhua Finance and Economics School
시험을 치르는 학생들 신화재경대학원
are really lucky.
정말 행운아야.
[Wishing everyone success in the college entrance exam]
[모두의 성공을 기원합니다 대학 입시에서]
Sold out?
매진되었나요?
[Hope you can get good results]
[좋은 결과 있기를 바랍니다]
Sold out!
매진!
That's wonderful.
정말 훌륭해요.
Congratulations.
축하합니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Dad, why don't you understand me at all?
아빠, 왜 제 말을 전혀 이해하지 못하시나요?
Have you had enough?
충분히 지냈나요?
Have I had enough?
나는 충분히 먹었습니까?
Why do you always think
왜 항상 생각하는 거야
I'm messing around?
내가 장난을 치고 있는 걸까?
I've been to Kuanli so many times,
나는 관리에 여러 번 가봤어,
but no one ever told me
하지만 아무도 나에게 말한 적이 없어
that the Venture Capital Summit was moved to early June.
벤처 캐피탈 서밋 6월 초로 변경되었습니다.
Why?
왜요?
The reason they dare to treat me like this
그들이 감히 나를 이렇게 대하는 이유
is because you
당신이
have never stood on my side.
한 번도 내 편에 서본 적이 없어요.
Bastard! You're useless,
개자식! 넌 쓸모없어,
but you blame it on me.
하지만 당신은 그것을 나에게 비난합니다.
Duan Aoxiang, listen!
Duan Aoxiang, 들어보세요!
Kuanli Group is not your playground.
관리그룹은 당신의 놀이터가 아닙니다.
Doing business is not playing a game.
사업을 한다는 것은 게임을 하는 것이 아닙니다.
No one can achieve a stunning success.
누구도 할 수 없어 놀라운 성공을 거두십시오.
You have a good hand.
당신은 좋은 손을 가지고 있습니다.
Give it to me if you don't know how to play.
나에게 줘 플레이하는 방법을 모른다면.
I have plenty of talents.
나는 재능이 많아요.
Who is it?
누구입니까?
Only an attendant came up with me just now.
수행원만 지금 막 나한테 왔어.
I let her go down first.
나는 그녀를 먼저 내려 놓았습니다.
No one else heard it except me.
나 외에는 아무도 그것을 듣지 못했습니다.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
걱정하지 마세요. 아무에게도 말하지 않겠습니다.
Come in.
들어오세요.
I'll have an attendant come and clean up.
직원을 불러서 청소하도록 하겠습니다.
Thanks.
감사합니다.
[Li Qiaoqi]
[리 차오치]
Miyu, you were amazing.
미유, 넌 정말 대단했어.
I'm so happy for you.
정말 기뻐요.
[Yin Xiang]
[인샹]
Miyu, you were so beautiful in the live stream.
미유, 넌 정말 아름다웠어 라이브 스트림에서.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[Xu Miyu]
[쉬미유]
[Lu Xiaoyan]
[루샤오옌]
You are great, Ms. Xu.
당신은 훌륭해요, Ms. Xu.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[Xu Miyu]
[쉬미유]
[Dianjiangchun Studio]
[Dianjiangchun 스튜디오]
[Light up life and spread the beauty]
[생명을 밝히고 아름다움을 널리 전하다]
[Ji Feng]
[지펑]
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I'm here to welcome the great contributor to Purong Hotel.
나는 환영하러 왔습니다 푸롱 호텔의 큰 공헌자.
By the way,
그런데,
I didn't have time to ask for instructions.
시간이 없었어요 지시를 요청합니다.
I just acted on my own.
나는 단지 내 마음대로 행동했을 뿐이다.
You did a very good job.
당신은 아주 좋은 일을 했습니다.
Are you free later?
나중에 시간 되세요?
I booked a restaurant.
레스토랑을 예약했어요.
I have something to say to you.
당신에게 할 말이 있습니다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
[ROSE GARDEN]
[장미정원]
I just told Hailin to keep you here.
방금 Hailin에게 당신을 여기에 두라고 말했습니다.
I didn't expect you to leave so quickly.
당신이 그렇게 빨리 떠날 줄은 몰랐어요.
Congratulations.
축하해요.
You made a great contribution to Purong.
푸롱에 큰 공헌을 하셨습니다.
I should thank you for cooperating with me.
나는 당신에게 감사해야한다 나와 협력합니다.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have gotten such a good result.
그렇지 않으면 우리는 없었을 것입니다 너무 좋은 결과를 얻었습니다.
Do you want to go for a drink later?
나중에 한잔 하러 갈래?
Consider it a celebration.
그것을 축하라고 생각하십시오.
How about you?
당신은 어떤가요?
As Purong's representative,
푸롱의 대표로서
do you want to come along?
같이 갈래?
I almost forgot. Thank you so much today.
나는 거의 잊었다. 오늘 정말 감사했습니다.
Thank you for your help.
도움을 주셔서 감사합니다.
Don't change the subject on purpose.
일부러 주제를 바꾸지 마세요.
Are you coming or not?
오실 건가요, 안 오실 건가요?
We can talk at the dinner table.
우리는 저녁 식탁에서 이야기를 나눌 수 있어요.
It wasn't easy to organize this.
이것을 정리하는 것이 쉽지 않았습니다.
You wouldn't reject me, would you?
당신은 나를 거부하지 않을 것입니다, 그렇죠?
Of course not.
물론 그렇지 않습니다.
Then, thank you, Ms. Jiang.
그럼 감사합니다, Jiang 씨.
Right.
오른쪽.
How about you?
당신은 어떤가요?
Zhichun, we have to go.
지춘아, 우리는 가야 해.
Then I'll drive.
그럼 내가 운전할게.
Take my car.
내 차를 가져가세요.
You can call a designated driver to drive your car back later.
대리운전자를 부르시면 됩니다 나중에 차를 몰고 돌아가려고요.
Let's go. I'll book a restaurant.
갑시다. 레스토랑을 예약할게요.
[Xu Miyu]
[쉬미유]
Let's leave together when this is over.
이 일이 끝나면 함께 떠나자.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Ladies, here are the menus.
숙녀분들, 여기 메뉴가 있습니다.
Ms. Xu, do you have any dietary restrictions?
쉬 씨, 그렇죠? 식단 제한이 있나요?
I'm fine with anything.
나는 무엇이든 괜찮습니다.
Their beef tartare is quite good.
그들의 쇠고기 타르타르는 꽤 좋습니다.
Why don't we try it?
시도해 보는 게 어때요?
Sure.
확신하는.
What other appetizers would you like?
다른 전채 요리는 무엇을 원하시나요?
I'd like to try the Farmhouse Soup.
농가 수프를 먹어보고 싶어요.
All right. We'll have three bowls of Farmhouse Soup.
괜찮은. 우리는 세 그릇 먹을 거예요 농가 수프.
And a Chicken with Hangzhou Chili.
그리고 항저우 칠리를 곁들인 닭고기.
And you?
당신은요?
Tomato and shredded pork noodles.
토마토와 잘게 썬 돼지고기 국수.
You still dislike
아직도 싫어하는구나
their cream spaghetti?
크림 스파게티?
Ms. Xu, what else would you like to order?
Xu 씨, 또 무엇을 주문하시겠습니까?
One Caesar Salad, please.
시저 샐러드 하나 주세요.
I remember there is mustard in Caesar Salad, right?
머스타드가 있었던걸로 기억하는데 시저 샐러드에 있지?
Yes.
예.
Sorry, Ms. Xu.
미안해요, 쉬 씨.
Ji Feng is allergic to mustard.
Ji Feng은 겨자 알레르기가 있습니다.
Should we change another one?
다른 것을 바꿔야 할까요?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Let us take this.
이것을 가져 갑시다.
We'll have one Caesar Salad.
시저 샐러드 하나 드세요.
I can eat a little bit now.
이제 조금 먹을 수 있어요.
What else do you want to order?
또 무엇을 주문하고 싶으신가요?
Enough for me.
나에게는 충분합니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
That's all for now.
지금은 그게 전부입니다.
Enjoy your meal.
식사를 즐기십시오.
Okay. Thank you.
좋아요. 감사합니다.
Cherish your free time.
자유시간을 소중히 여기세요.
Since you won the battle today,
오늘 전투에서 승리했으므로
you'll be busy in the following days.
당신은 다음 날부터 바빠질 것입니다.
The real preparation work will begin the day after tomorrow.
본격적인 준비작업 모레부터 시작됩니다.
At that time,
당시
we welcome you to shoot and collect more video materials.
촬영에 오신 것을 환영합니다. 더 많은 영상자료를 모아보세요.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
For this promotion,
이번 프로모션에서는
I'll follow up on the whole process.
전체 과정을 자세히 살펴보겠습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Would you like desserts?
디저트를 드시겠어요?
No need, thank you.
필요없습니다. 감사합니다.
I know girls can't resist desserts.
나는 여자들이 디저트를 거부할 수 없다는 것을 안다.
but their dessert tastes so-so.
하지만 그들의 디저트 맛은 그저 그렇습니다.
I know a place nearby that I ordered from before.
나는 그 근처에 한 곳을 알아요 예전부터 주문했는데
After we buy what we want online
원하는 것을 온라인으로 구매한 후
we can let Ji Feng pick it up.
Ji Feng이 가져가도록 하면 됩니다.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
see if there's anything you want to eat.
먹고 싶은 게 있는지 살펴보세요.
[Sesame Crisp Biscuit] [Kai Kou Xiao]
[참깨 크리스프 비스킷] [카이 코우 샤오]
Then, thank you, Mr. Ji,
그럼 지 선생님, 감사합니다
for making a trip for us.
우리를 위해 여행을 해주셔서.
No problem.
괜찮아요.
I'll send you the screenshot.
스크린샷을 보내드리겠습니다.
They serve food very fast.
그들은 음식을 매우 빠르게 제공합니다.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Ms. Jiang knows this restaurant very well.
Jiang 씨는 이 식당을 아주 잘 알고 있습니다.
It's not your first time here, is it?
여기가 처음이 아니죠?
You saw through it.
당신은 그것을 꿰뚫어 보았습니다.
You are very familiar with everything here.
당신은 매우 잘 알고 있습니다 여기에 모든 것이 있습니다.
I've been here many times before.
나는 전에 여러 번 여기에 왔습니다.
Do you know
알고 계세요
when the first time I came here was?
내가 여기 처음 왔을 때가 언제였지?
It was when I won the best debater for the first time
제가 최고의 토론자상을 받았을 때였어요. 처음으로
in a debate competition in college.
대학 토론 대회에서.
At that time, Ji Feng didn't have much money.
그 당시, Ji Feng은 돈이 많지 않았습니다.
He used his first internship salary
그는 첫 번째 인턴십 급여를 사용했습니다
to bring me here to celebrate.
축하하기 위해 나를 여기로 데려오려고요.
Congratulations to Miss Jiang Zhichun for winning the best debater.
장지춘 선생님 축하드립니다 최고의 토론자 우승을 위해.
And congratulations to you for
And congratulations to you for
getting your first salary in life.
축하드립니다. 인생 첫 월급을 받다.
Cheers.
건배.
I've started getting the hang of it lately.
나는 시작했다 최근에 요령을 얻고 있습니다.
If everything goes well,
모든 일이 순조롭게 진행된다면
I can become a full-time employee after a few more job rotations.
정규직이 될 수 있어요 몇 번의 직무 순환 후에.
Tastes good.
맛이 좋다.
The dishes just now also tasted good.
지금 막 나온 요리들 맛도 좋았습니다.
Let's come to this place often, okay?
우리 여기 자주 오자, 알았지?
Sure.
확신하는.
My boyfriend, you are excellent.
내 남자친구, 당신은 정말 훌륭해요.
I think you'll definitely become a full-time employee.
내 생각엔 넌 분명 그럴 거야 정규직 직원이 됩니다.
If you perform well,
실적이 좋으면
you might even be promoted straight to manager.
승진할 수도 있다 바로 매니저에게.
I'll try my best.
최선을 다하겠습니다.
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
Too greasy.
너무 기름기가 많아요.
Really? Let me taste it.
정말? 맛보게 해주세요.
I think it's pretty good.
꽤 좋은 것 같아요.
Then, I'll order it for you next time.
그럼 다음에는 제가 주문할게요.
I dislike it.
나는 그것을 싫어한다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Drink some water.
물을 좀 마셔보세요.
At that time, I thought
그때 나는
I was so lucky.
나는 정말 운이 좋았다.
At the right time,
적절한 시기에
I was staying with the right person.
나는 올바른 사람과 함께 머물고있었습니다.
Even the randomly chosen restaurant
무작위로 선택한 레스토랑도
was so perfect.
정말 완벽했어요.
Everything was just right.
모든 것이 옳았습니다.
I didn't expect this restaurant to
이 식당이 이렇게 될 줄은 몰랐어요
have been open for over a decade.
오픈한 지 십년이 넘었습니다.
Actually, later on,
실제로 나중에는
I came here by myself a few times.
나는 여기에 몇 번 혼자 왔어요.
Maybe because my mood was different,
기분이 달라서 그럴 수도 있겠네요
the dishes didn't taste the same as before.
그 요리는 같은 맛이 아니었어 이전처럼.
Actually, there's no such thing as "just right."
사실 별거 없어요 "맞아요."
All the perfection
완벽해
was just him accommodating me.
단지 그 사람이 나를 수용하고 있었을 뿐이에요.
He is great. But I didn't cherish him.
그는 훌륭합니다. 하지만 나는 그를 소중히 여기지 않았습니다.
So I regret it very much now.
그래서 지금은 많이 후회하고 있어요.
I really want to mend our relationship.
나는 정말로 우리 관계를 고치고 싶습니다.
Do you think it's still possible?
아직도 가능하다고 생각하시나요?
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
Do you feel disillusioned?
환멸을 느끼시나요?
A blogger who has always flaunted being an independent woman
언제나 그랬던 블로거 독립적인 여성임을 과시했습니다
unexpectedly, in real life,
예기치 않게 현실에서는
is so hesitant and conflicted
너무 주저하고 갈등이 많아
when it comes to relationships.
관계에 관해서라면.
No.
아니요.
Thank you for your honesty, Ms. Jiang.
정직하게 말해 주셔서 감사합니다, Jiang 씨.
But I think
하지만 내 생각에는
the choice of your relationship is
당신의 관계의 선택은
in the hands of you two.
너희 둘의 손에.
I don't know much about your past,
나는 당신의 과거에 대해 잘 모릅니다
and I won't interfere in your future.
그리고 나는 당신의 미래에 간섭하지 않을 것입니다.
If you have something to say,
하고 싶은 말이 있으면
I think you'd better tell Mr. Ji directly.
내 생각에는 지씨에게 직접 말씀하시는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
Here you are.
여기 있어요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Where is Miyu?
미유는 어디에 있나요?
Ms. Xu said there's something at the hotel,
Xu 씨가 뭔가 있다고 하더군요 호텔에서
so she went back to handle it.
그래서 그녀는 그것을 처리하기 위해 다시 돌아갔습니다.
Did she just leave?
그녀가 방금 떠났나요?
Ji Feng!
지펑!
Miyu!
미유!
I'll take you back.
내가 다시 데려다줄게
No need. I've booked a rideshare.
필요하지 않습니다. 공유 차량을 예약했어요.
The car is already here.
차는 이미 와 있어요.
The pickup point is right here.
픽업 장소는 바로 여기입니다.
Did she say something to you?
그녀가 당신에게 뭐라고 말했나요?
No.
아니요.
There is something in the hotel.
호텔에 뭔가가 있습니다.
I need to go back and handle it.
돌아가서 처리해야 해요.
I'll leave it to you guys.
여러분에게 맡기겠습니다.
Miyu, I have something to tell you.
미유야, 너한테 할 말이 있어.
Let's talk another day.
다른 날에 얘기하자.
I'm tired today.
오늘은 피곤해요.
♪ A flicker of dim light ♪
♪ 희미한 빛의 깜박임 ♪
♪ A bowl of warm soup ♪
♪ 따뜻한 국 한 그릇 ♪
♪ People in the city ♪
♪ 도시의 사람들 ♪
♪ Squeezing into the hustle and bustle ♪
♪ 소란스러운 상황 속으로 비집고 들어갑니다 ♪
Actually, I know very well that
사실 나도 잘 알고 있어
things turning out like this
일이 이렇게 됐어
♪ The palms of time ♪
♪ 시간의 손바닥 ♪
isn't anyone's fault.
누구의 잘못도 아닙니다.
It's just that a relationship among three people is too complicated.
그냥 그런 관계야 세 사람 사이에는 너무 복잡합니다.
♪ Grinding away the simple days ♪
♪ 단순한 일상을 날려버리세요 ♪
Those back-and-forth confrontations
앞뒤로 대립하는 것
have drained too much of my energy.
내 에너지를 너무 많이 소모했습니다.
♪ Sprinkling them into this busy world ♪
♪ 바쁜 세상에 뿌려주세요 ♪
Maybe it's not that hard to cheer up and face it.
어쩌면 그렇게 어렵지는 않을지도 몰라 힘내서 맞서세요.
♪ To be tasted, bit by bit ♪
♪ 조금씩 맛볼 수 있도록 ♪
But right now,
하지만 지금은
do I really need a relationship like this?
나한테 정말 이런 관계가 필요한 걸까?
♪ Embracing this radiant world ♪
♪ 이 빛나는 세상을 끌어안아 ♪
♪ Keeps the heart from fading to grey ♪
♪ 마음이 회색으로 변하는 것을 방지합니다 ♪
♪ Life's joy, sorrow, cold, and warmth ♪
♪ 인생의 기쁨, 슬픔, 추위, 따뜻함 ♪
♪ Intertwined within the mundane ♪
♪ 일상 속에 얽혀 있습니다 ♪
♪ Let us bravely gather up ♪
♪ 용감하게 모이자 ♪
♪ The forgotten past ♪
♪ 잊혀진 과거 ♪
♪ There may be regrets ♪
♪ 후회할 수도 있어요 ♪
♪ There may be loneliness ♪
♪ 외로움이 있을 수도 있어요 ♪
The stationery delivery is here.
문구류 배송이 왔습니다.
Just put it here.
그냥 여기에 넣어두세요.
Over here.
여기요.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Let's pack up the stationery sets.
편지지 세트를 꾸리자.
Each requires three pencils,
각각 연필 3개가 필요합니다.
one eraser,
지우개 하나,
one pencil sharpener,
연필깎이 하나,
two pens,
펜 두 개,
one notebook,
노트북 한 개,
plus a box of binder clips.
그리고 바인더 클립 상자도 있습니다.
We have to prepare 600 sets in total.
총 600세트를 준비해야 해요.
Let's do it.
해보자.
Okay.
좋아요.
Tell me when you're done.
끝나면 말해주세요.
Ms. He,
그 씨
the writing desks and stationery for exam-takers
책상과 수험생을 위한 문구류
have all been prepared.
모두 준비되었습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Ms. Xu instructed us
Xu 씨가 우리에게 지시했습니다.
to remember to test the internet speed at noon.
기억하다 정오에 인터넷 속도를 테스트해 보세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
Morning.
아침.
Hello, Ms. Xu.
안녕하세요, 쉬 씨.
Everyone will have to work hard today.
오늘은 다들 열심히 일해야겠습니다.
Guests will come here
손님이 여기로 올 것이다
one after another to check in shortly.
곧 체크인하기 위해 차례로.
Remember to carefully check
주의 깊게 확인하세요
exam-takers' admission tickets.
수험생 입장권.
In addition,
게다가
report any guests with special needs immediately.
손님이 있으면 신고하세요 특별한 도움이 필요한 경우 즉시.
We must meet the guests' needs
우리는 손님의 요구를 충족해야 합니다
as quickly as possible.
가능한 한 빨리.
Yes.
예.
Welcome.
환영.
Here are our ID cards
여기 우리 신분증이 있어요
and the child's admission ticket.
그리고 어린이 입장권.
Okay, please wait a moment.
알겠습니다. 잠시만 기다려 주세요.
Stop looking at your phone.
전화기를 보지 마세요.
Pay the bill with your credit card.
신용카드로 요금을 결제하세요.
Here is your bill.
여기 청구서가 있습니다.
Please sign it.
서명해 주세요.
Why is this price?
왜 이 가격인가요?
Didn't we agree on a half-price discount?
우리는 반값 할인에 동의하지 않았나요?
It is half price,
반값이에요,
but you booked the executive floor.
하지만 당신은 귀빈층을 예약했어요.
This is the price for a room on the executive floor after the discount.
이것은 방의 가격입니다 할인 후 이그제큐티브 층에 있습니다.
You booked the executive floor?
귀빈층을 예약하셨나요?
Our child's college entrance exam is
우리 아이 대학 입시는
the most important thing.
가장 중요한 것.
Of course, we have to stay in the best room.
물론, 우리는 가장 좋은 방에 머물러야 해요.
This is a five-star hotel.
이곳은 5성급 호텔입니다.
The accommodation and food are fine.
숙소와 음식은 괜찮습니다.
Why did you book an executive suite?
왜 이그제큐티브 스위트룸을 예약했나요?
Why can't we book an executive suite?
왜 이그제큐티브 스위트룸을 예약할 수 없나요?
You don't usually save money.
당신은 보통 돈을 저축하지 않습니다.
Our kid is taking the college entrance exam.
우리 아이는 대학 입학 시험을 치르는 중.
For such a big deal,
이렇게 큰 일이라니,
you're being stingy?
너 인색한 거야?
What kind of father are you?
당신은 어떤 아버지인가요?
I just don't think it's necessary.
나는 그것이 필요하다고 생각하지 않습니다.
Why isn't it necessary?
왜 필요하지 않습니까?
You snore so loudly at night.
당신은 밤에 코를 너무 크게 골어요.
If I don't get a suite,
스위트룸을 얻지 못하면
what if our child can't sleep well?
우리 아이가 잠을 잘 못 잔다면?
Then, you shouldn't have let my dad come.
그렇다면 우리 아빠를 오지 말았어야지.
Liu Yuze, just be quiet.
Liu Yuze, 조용히 하세요.
Sorry to interrupt.
방해해서 죄송합니다.
How about this?
이건 어때요?
Please follow me to the executive floor
나를 따라 임원층으로 가주세요
to check in.
체크인하러.
Come, this way please.
이쪽으로 오세요.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
Hurry up and go to your room so you can start studying.
빨리 가서 네 방으로 가 그래서 공부를 시작할 수 있습니다.
I got you such a nice room,
정말 좋은 방을 구해 줬어요
but you're ungrateful.
하지만 당신은 배은망덕 해요.
Welcome.
환영.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
The network signal for the rooms on the east side
네트워크 신호 동쪽에 있는 방들
has already been tested.
이미 테스트되었습니다.
Guests can check in now.
지금 체크인하실 수 있습니다.
The workers of the Engineering Department are testing the west side.
엔지니어링 부서의 직원 서쪽을 테스트 중입니다.
It should be done soon.
곧 완료되어야합니다.
Okay, I'll leave this to you.
좋아요, 이건 당신에게 맡기겠습니다.
By the way, this student has some hearing problems.
그건 그렇고, 이 학생은 청각에 문제가 있습니다.
Please take extra care of him.
그를 특별히 돌봐주세요.
Don't worry, leave it to me.
걱정하지 마세요. 저에게 맡겨주세요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
a guest in the lobby said
로비에 있던 손님이 말했다
they didn't get the livestream booking
실시간 스트리밍 예약을 받지 못했어
but booked an exam-taker room through the platform.
하지만 수험생 방을 예약했어 플랫폼을 통해.
They want to know whether they can enjoy the discount.
그들은 여부를 알고 싶어 그들은 할인을 즐길 수 있습니다.
Copy that. I'm coming down now.
복사하세요. 나는 지금 내려간다.
I'll go then.
그럼 내가 갈게.
Get back to work.
다시 일하세요.
The discount for exam-taker rooms on the platform
수험실 할인 플랫폼에서
and those booked through Dianjiangchun's stream is the same.
그리고 예약하신 분들은 Dianjiangchun의 흐름도 마찬가지입니다.
What about the stream's half-hour voucher?
스트림의 30분 이용권은 어떻습니까?
That takes off 20 yuan.
20 위안이 걸립니다.
This is an exclusive discount of the live-streaming room.
의 독점 할인입니다. 라이브 스트리밍 룸.
Purong can't provide you with this discount.
푸롱은 제공할 수 없습니다 이 할인을 받으세요.
How about this?
이건 어때요?
After you check in,
체크인한 후,
we'll give you a voucher for the hotel's Chinese restaurant
우리는 당신에게 바우처를 줄 것입니다 호텔의 중국 식당
as a token of our appreciation.
감사의 표시로.
Does it work for you?
당신에게 효과가 있나요?
Okay.
좋아요.
Remember to send it to our room later.
나중에 우리 방으로 보내주세요.
Okay, no problem.
알았어, 문제없어.
Come on, I'll arrange it.
어서, 내가 정리할게.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Give this guest
이 손님에게 주세요
a 30-yuan voucher.
30위안 상품권.
Okay, no problem.
알았어, 문제없어.
Be quick.
빨리.
Watch the heat here.
여기 더위 조심하세요.
Don't put too much oil, okay?
기름은 너무 많이 넣지 마세요.
How long will it take to be ready?
준비하는 데 얼마나 걸리나요?
Ten minutes.
10분.
Guo?
구오?
I'm here.
나는 여기 있다.
Get as much of that as you have, hurry up.
당신이 가지고 있는 만큼 많이 얻으세요. 서두르세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
We still need two people here.
여기에는 아직 두 사람이 필요합니다.
Let someone come here quickly.
누군가 빨리 여기로 오도록 해주세요.
Ya?
당신?
-Qiaoqi. -Ya.
-차오치. -당신.
It's today's set meal.
오늘의 정식입니다.
Where's the Yan Du Xian?
Yan Du Xian은 어디에 있습니까?
Here comes the Yan Du Xian.
Yan Du Xian이 왔습니다.
Serve it just like this.
이렇게 서비스해 보세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Please enjoy today's set meal.
오늘의 정식을 즐겨주세요.
Braised pork ribs. I like it.
돼지갈비찜. 좋아요.
We'll have a cold appetizer platter,
차가운 애피타이저 플래터를 먹겠습니다
pork potstickers,
돼지고기 냄비 스티커,
scallion oil noodles and mung bean soup.
파기름국수와 녹두국물.
Okay.
좋아요.
Try it.
시도해 보세요.
We'd like a portion of that set meal too.
우리도 그 정식의 일부를 원합니다.
It looks quite delicious.
꽤 맛있어 보이네요.
All right.
괜찮은.
Hello, distinguished guests.
안녕하세요, 내외 귀빈 여러분.
Kind reminder from Purong Hotel:
Purong Hotel의 친절한 알림:
it's morning now.
지금은 아침이에요.
The buffet restaurant opens at 6:30.
뷔페 레스토랑은 6시 30분에 오픈합니다.
You can come to have your breakfast.
아침식사를 하러 오셔도 됩니다.
If the buffet restaurant is
뷔페 레스토랑이
short of people,
사람이 부족해요
you can go help out.
가서 도와주면 돼.
I often help serve dishes.
나는 종종 설거지를 돕습니다.
Zhichun.
지춘.
Then, you can go back to work.
그런 다음 다시 일을 하시면 됩니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I'm here to shoot some footage.
저는 영상을 좀 찍으러 왔습니다.
Did you get what you needed?
필요한 것을 얻으셨나요?
I got a lot.
나는 많이 얻었다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Take your time shooting.
천천히 촬영하세요.
I'll be leaving.
나는 떠날 것이다.
Find Xue Rui if you need anything.
필요한 것이 있으면 Xue Rui를 찾아보세요.
Let's rest for a while
잠시 쉬자
and shoot when exam-takers come back.
수험생이 돌아오면 쏴보세요.
They are back.
그들은 돌아왔다.
Everyone, get ready.
여러분, 준비하세요.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Go. Go. Go.
가다. 가다. 가다.
Come, serve the food.
와서 음식을 대접하세요.
Come on. Here
어서 해봐요. 여기
Come help.
도와주세요.
Go.
가다.
Serve the food.
음식을 서빙하세요.
[Xu Miyu]
[쉬미유]
During the college entrance exam,
대학 입시 중에
Mr. Ji, you don't have other plans?
지 선생님, 다른 계획은 없으신가요?
I'm busy.
나는 바쁘다.
Meiqi, two Americanos, please.
메이치 아메리카노 두 잔 주세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
What about you?
당신은 어때요?
What are you busy with?
무슨 일로 바쁜가요?
I thought I'd be very busy,
매우 바쁠 거라 생각했는데
but I overthought it.
하지만 나는 그것을 지나치게 생각했습니다.
Mr. Ji, your Americanos.
미스터 지, 당신의 아메리카노.
Actually, sometimes,
사실 가끔
I really envy you.
정말 당신이 부러워요.
The heir of Kuanli Group envies me?
관리그룹 후계자가 나를 부러워한다고?
Don't think I can't tell that you're being sarcastic.
생각하지 마세요 나는 당신이 냉소적이라고 말할 수 없습니다.
I didn't mean that at all.
그런 뜻은 전혀 아니었어요.
I just think
내 생각엔
it would be great to be like you,
당신처럼 되면 좋을 것 같아요,
who can do whatever you want to do.
당신이 하고 싶은 일은 무엇이든 할 수 있는 사람.
The feeling of fighting for something for yourself
위해 싸우는 느낌 너 자신을 위한 뭔가를
must be really good, right?
정말 좋을 텐데요, 그렇죠?
What are you trying to say?
무슨 말을 하려는 걸까요?
Honestly, I don't know what I want to say.
솔직히 무슨 말을 하고 싶은지 모르겠습니다.
Ever since I was born,
나는 태어났을 때부터
I've been doing what my dad wanted me to do.
나는 계속해서 아버지가 나에게 하고 싶었던 일.
He asks for so much.
그는 너무 많은 것을 요구합니다.
I can never satisfy him.
나는 결코 그를 만족시킬 수 없습니다.
I look like a loser.
나는 패배자처럼 보인다.
Mr. Duan.
듀안 씨.
If you give up so early,
너무 일찍 포기한다면,
I'll think that in terms of our VAM agreement,
측면에서는 그렇게 생각하겠습니다 우리의 VAM 계약,
I have already won.
나는 이미 이겼습니다.
How could that be?
어떻게 그럴 수 있니?
Our hotel has never been so empty.
우리 호텔은 이렇게 비어 있었던 적이 없습니다.
Only for now.
지금으로서만.
At noon,
정오에
they all rushed back to eat and sleep.
그들은 모두 서둘러 먹고 자러 돌아갔습니다.
It was packed with people over there.
거기는 사람들로 꽉 차 있었어요.
So scary.
너무 무서워요.
Xiaoyan,
샤오옌,
how did your cousin do on his exam this morning?
네 사촌은 어떻게 됐어? 오늘 아침 시험에?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
He didn't say anything when I asked him.
내가 물었을 때 그는 아무 말도 하지 않았다.
He used his phone all noon,
그는 정오 내내 휴대전화를 사용했어요
checking answers with his classmates.
반 친구들과 답을 확인하는 중입니다.
Looks like they're back.
그들이 돌아온 것 같습니다.
They are back.
그들은 돌아왔다.
HSKP Department. HSKP Department.
HSKP 부서. HSKP 부서.
Finish the turndown service as soon as possible.
턴다운 서비스를 완료하세요 가능한 한 빨리.
The guests are back.
손님이 돌아 왔습니다.
Ready? If so, send them out right away.
준비가 된? 그렇다면 즉시 보내십시오.
Is tonight's supper menu ready?
오늘 저녁 메뉴는 준비됐나요?
Right here.
바로 여기입니다.
You can take a look, I'll deal with something.
살펴보실 수 있습니다. 내가 뭔가를 처리하겠습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Ms. Xu. Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨. 쉬 씨.
A guest at the front desk is complaining about a lost valuable.
프런트 데스크에 손님이 계십니다. 귀중품을 잃어버렸다고 불평합니다.
Got it, I'll be right there.
알겠습니다. 바로 거기로 갈게요.
My son's hearing aid was customized.
내 아들의 보청기가 맞춤 제작되었습니다.
You just said you hadn't found it. That is it?
방금 못 찾았다고 하셨어요. 그게 다야?
What am I supposed to do?
나는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
What about tomorrow's English listening exam?
어떻습니까? 내일 영어 듣기 시험?
What is my son going to do?
내 아들은 무엇을 할 것인가?
Ma'am, please calm down.
부인, 진정하세요.
What is the point of giving me water?
나에게 물을 주는 것이 무슨 소용이 있는가?
What I want is my son's hearing aid.
제가 원하는 것은 제 아들의 보청기입니다.
Ma'am, please calm down first.
부인, 먼저 진정하세요.
I'll help you solve whatever the problem is.
해결 도와드릴게요 문제가 무엇이든.